Whose idea was it to put
everybody in the diner on skates?
Some idiot customer put a suggestion
in the suggestion box.
-Oh, my God! They took my idea!
-That was you?
Okay, there you go.
Rachel, I made you cocoa.
Oh, that's so....
Oh, my God! Are you guys okay?
Oh, my.
The One With a Chick and a Duck
You know, with that goatee,
you kind of look like Satan.
So that's why the priest
threw holy water on me.
You have to cheer up.
You should come out with Ross and me.
Anything is better than sitting
here crying all day about Kate.
I was crying because
nobody believed Quincy's theory.
I'm gonna be on TV!
No way!
They're putting together a panel
to talk about the fossils in Peru.
The Discovery Channel's filming it!
Oh, my God!
Who's gonna watch that?
Thanks. You ready to go?
I saw a girl with that vest.
Thanks.
Most of us think of chocolate and
baskets as traditional Easter gifts.
Some people insist on
giving live chicks as presents.
Unfortunately, most of these guys
won't live to see the 4th of July.
As a result of improper care,
they will be dead.
You guys got any of those baby chicks?
I was watching this commercial on TV,
and, man, those things are cute!
Pete, you're back!
Hey, check this out!
Skates!
You're sturdier than Chandler.
He crumbled like a piece of paper.
How was your trip?
What'd you bring me?
Hotel toiletries from Japan!
These are gonna go
in my permanent collection.
-Want some coffee?
-That'd be great.
Regular or decaf?
Whichever's closest.
-Ask me what I did today.
-What did you do today?
I bought a restaurant
and I'd like you to be the chef.
Can you believe he
offered me a restaurant?
What a jerk.
You want me to kick his ass?
It's been my dream since
I got my first Easy-Bake Oven...
...and opened Easy-Monica's Bakery.
I would kill for this job.
I can totally do this job...
...and God knows, I've paid my dues.
But Pete's doing this
because he has a crush on me.
And you're still not
attracted to him at all?
How could I accept a restaurant
from him? I can't.
I couldn't accept a necklace
from Stu Vincent in the 7th grade.
But, Mon, that was totally different.
He was your health teacher.
What, honey?
My side hurts from when
you crashed into me.
Oh, God, I'm so sorry.
Oh, God!
Hey, you guys. Guess what?
Got a job on a riverboat?
I didn't wear this suit for a year,
because you hated it.
You're not my girlfriend
anymore, so....
I see. This suit is making a point.
Now that you're on your own, you're
free to look as stupid as you'd like.
You like it, right?
I like it even more on you
than I did on Colonel Sanders.
Ross, I'm kidding. Come here.
What were you gonna tell us?
Was it how you
invented the cotton gin?
So after you put the suggestion
in the box...
...how long did it take
for it to happen?
About three months.
So I guess that's about two weeks
before the topless thing kicks in.
I got you something.
Open it! Open it!
It's a chicken.
It's cute, huh?
You guys? Do you know
anything about chicks?
Fowl? No.
Women? No.
They are a huge responsibility.
Especially at this age.
They require constant care.
They need just the right food
and lots and lots of love.
Well, no problem there.
Easy, Lenny.
So, I mean, have you thought about it?
Okay, here's the thing.
Not "the thing."
I hate "the thing."
What's "the thing"?
I can't do it.
I'm sorry. I wish I could...
... but you have these feelings for me.
That's what you're worried about?
If that's the problem,
we've got no problem.
I was gonna tell you over dinner,
but I met somebody else, on my trip.
Her name's Ann. She's a journalist.
We met on the plane.
She wanted to finish off
my peanuts.
I thought she said something else.
We had a big laugh.
I got tired of waiting.
That's great. I'm sorry,
but I'm so happy for you.
-Now I can work for you!
-I guess you can.
Oh, my God! This is incredible!
You know what? I'm gonna roll
right into that office and quit!
All right!
Could you give me a little push?
Good luck!
I'm quitting!
I'm okay! I'm all right!
That's exciting.
You went to Japan, made up a woman.
What?
I'm just saying, this "woman,"
I mean, she's fictitious, no?
-Why would you say that?
-You're still into Monica.
You said there's somebody else
so she'd work with you.
If you spend time together,
maybe something might happen.
You're good. You're good.
No, I'm fairly intuitive. And psychic.
It's a substantial gift.
Can you promise me
that you won't tell her?
Absolutely. I promise.
Tell her what?
Thanks a lot.
No, I'm serious.
I'm intuitive, but my memory sucks.
Okay, but this is the last time.
With a chick-chick here
And a chick-chick there
Here a chick, there a chick
Everywhere a chick-chick
Chicken....
How's she doing?
She?
Don't you think it's a she?
I don't know.
I can't tell. Whatever it was
went back in too quickly.
I gotta change. I'm meeting
some of the cast for drinks.
Excuse me?
What?
I stayed home while
you were at rehearsal...
...so somebody could be here
with our chick.
Who was up from 2:00 this
morning until 5:00...
...trying to get her back to sleep?
You don't think I get up
when you get up?
Oh, here it comes.
Yes! Here it comes!
I'm stuck here all day!
And then you come in
and spend two seconds with us...
...and then expect to go off
gallivanting with your friends?
Well, I don't think so, mister!
I need to relax, okay?
I was working all day.
And you don't think
taking care of our chick is work?
That's not what I said.
I just meant
I know what you meant!
Did you notice that ever since
we got this chick...
...we've been fighting
a lot more than we used to?
I don't know, maybe we weren't
ready to have a chick.
I'll take her back tomorrow.
We'll get our $3 back?
I have that TV thing in two hours,
and I need your help.
What do you think?
This blue suit or this brown one?
The brown one brings out your eyes.
But your butt looks great
in the blue one.
Really?
That aspirin dance really works.
-ls that still...?
-I'm fine.
-No, you're not!
-Yes, I am.
Look, I'm fine.
Watch. Look at that.
You've got to go to a doctor, okay?
I have to get ready and go
to a dinner at my boss's house.
There's people there
that I have to meet.
I'm sure you'll make a great
impression. "Hi, I'm Rachel.
It's nice to meet you."
Come on, you probably
have a broken rib.
I'll go to the hospital tomorrow.
It'll still be broken then.
But you know, I could use a hand
getting ready.
Either help me, or go.
Fine. I'll go.
But before you go,
could you help me first?
Sure. I'll help you.
Good! Do you guys know how
to get a chick out of a VCR?
You know what?
I cannot do this with my left hand.
Would you please help me
with this too?
Let's use this brush.
-This stuff?
-Careful.
Light.
Just sweep it across the lid.
Just sweep it.
Sorry!
That's just poking me in the eye.
I'm sorry. Close....
-Just sweep it.
-I'm sweeping.
Sweep, sweep....
Now make it even,
because we don't....
I don't want it to be too much.
I want it to be subtle.
You don't wear enough of this.
Since when do you think
I don't wear enough of this?
Close your eye.
You're gonna like this better....
-Close, close.
-Blow it.
Because I think this will make you
a little more sophisticated.
Sophisticated like a hooker?
-Guess what I'm doing tonight.
-What?
I'm checking out
the restaurant with Pete.
Monica, I am so excited for you!
I have to tell you something.
What?
I can't tell you.
Wouldn't it be easier to tell
me something that you could tell me?
Well, sure, in a perfect world.
But no. I promised I wouldn't tell,
and I swore to all my Gods.
Does it have to do with
Ross and Rachel?
Does it have to do with Joey?
Does it have to do with Chandler
and that sock he keeps by his bed?
No, but let's come back to that later.
There you go!
Good enough for your party?
Sure.
Sure. I'll just sit next to
the transsexual from purchasing.
All right, I gotta go,
So good luck at the party.
Could you just stay
and help me get dressed?
Sure.
Great. Okay, just turn around.
What?
I don't want you to see me naked.
I've seen you naked a million times.
I ate hot fudge off you naked.
I sucked that mini-marshmallow
out of your bellybutton.
Yeah, but that was different.
We were going out then.
Now it's weird.
Rach, you know, I can see
you naked anytime I want.
What?
All I have to do is close my eyes.
See?
Ross, stop that!
Come on! Don't think of me
like that anymore.
Sorry. Nothing you can do about it.
It's one of my rights
as the ex-boyfriend.
Stop it! Cut it out! Cut it out!
I'm sorry. It will never happen
Wait a minute! Wait, wait....
Now there are 100 of you,
and I'm the king!
Would you grow up? It's no big deal.
All right. Fine.
See what you did?
I'm gonna be doing it by myself now.
Oh, my God. All right, look, look....
Easy. Easy.
You have to go to the hospital, okay?
I do. I really do.
I'll get your coat,
then I'll put you in a cab.
You're not gonna come with me?
Of course I am.
I just have to make a call.
Thank you.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry. I just can't go
to the hospital looking like this.
Does it involve travel?
Does it involve clogs?
Clogs or claws?
Clogs.
Claws?
So it doesn't involve Ross or Rachel
or Chandler or Joey.
What about Pete?
What is it?
-What about Pete?
-I don't know!
I feel like I'm talking to Lassie.
-Phoebe, would you just tell me?
-I can't!
-I gotta go.
-But you're so close!
Something to do
with Pete's company?
Go! You'll never get it!
I know.
See, yes. That's Yasmine Bleeth.
She's a completely different
kind of chick.
I love you both.
But in very different ways.
What are you doing?
You were gonna take her back.
I did. But the store
wouldn't take her back.
Then I took her to the shelter.
You know what I found out?
If they can't find a home for her,
they kill her!
I won't let that happen
to little Jasmine.
Good, good, because I was
kind of having second thoughts too.
And it's not just chicks.
It's all kinds of other animals.
That's horrible.
You did the right thing.
Thanks. I'm glad
you see it that way.
Funny story!
I don't believe this!
Look at this refrigerator!
It's gigantic!
I could live in this thing!
I'd be cold, but I'm always cold!
Oh, my God! Look at these spider
burners! I love spider burners!
So you like it?
It is so perfect!
Thank you so much.
You're welcome.
Did you just smell my hair?
No! No way! What?
-Oh, God.
-What?
You still have feelings for me.
I'm just excited about the restaurant,
that's all.
I love you. Is that so bad?
No, it's not bad.
It's not bad at all.
It's really nice.
The only one who stands to get hurt
is me, and I'm okay with that.
You may be okay with getting hurt...
...but I am not okay with being
the one who hurts you.
That's why I can't take this job.
What?
We probably shouldn't
see each other anymore.
I'm sorry.
I mean, if that's
really what you want, okay.
I'm sorry things
Shut up for a second
and let me just see something.
You'd tell me the truth?
Rach, you can't look fat in an x-ray.
Now you stay out here
and you think about what you did!
-That's a duck!
-That's a bad duck!
How'd the thing go tonight, Ross?
What thing? What thing?
Nothing. There was this thing
at the museum. Come on.
Easy.
Now, when you come back, I hope you
remember that that chick is not a toy!
What "thing"? What is this "thing"?
I was kind of supposed to be on TV
tonight for the Discovery Channel.
Oh, my God!
Ross, why didn't you tell me that?
I knew that if I told you,
you'd make me go...
...and I knew you needed someone
to be with you tonight. Come on.
-I cannot believe you.
-What?
That is the sweetest thing.
You should get some sleep.
Sorry I spoiled your evening.
As long as you're okay.
So I'll see you tomorrow.
See you.
What did you do?
What you doing?
Having a swim.
What about the chick?
Chicks don't swim.
Are you sure?
I don't know.
-Should we try?
-Sure.
See, I told you.
They don't swim.
Well, give him a minute.
It's okay.
It's okay, baby, baby, baby.